Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Technical Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Annual report input, 1984-1987; Accession 1997-A-020
  - Latin American collection (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Kline Science library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Kline Science library, G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Kline Science library, S, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Latin American collection (SML), G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Latin American collection (SML), S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Law library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Law library, S, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Lewis' Walpole library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Lewis' Walpole library, G, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Lewis' Walpole library, S, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Manuscripts and Archives department (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Manuscripts and Archives department (SML), G, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Manuscripts and Archives department (SML), S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Map collection (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Map collection (SML), G, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Map collection (SML), S, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Mathematics library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Mathematics library, G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Mathematics library, S, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Medical library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Medical library, G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Medical library, S, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Music library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Music library, G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Music library, S, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Numismatic collection (SML), Undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Numismatic collection (SML), G, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Numismatic collection (SML), S, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Ornithology library, Undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Ornithology library, G, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Ornithology library, S, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Reference department (SML), G, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - General appropriation, 1967-1968 (Box 1A, Folder 1)
  - Ornithology library, S, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Palmer-Schreiber library, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Personnel office (SML), Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Personnel office (SML), G, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Philosophy library, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Philosophy library, S, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Preservation department (SML), including conservation, photographic service, preparations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Preservation department (SML), G; including conservation, photographic service, preparations, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Preservation department (SML), S; including conservation, photographic service, and preparations, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Reference department (SML), 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Seeley G. Mudd library, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Seeley G. Mudd library, G, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Seeley G. Mudd library, S, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Semitic reference (SML), G and S, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sinological seminar (SML), G and S, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Slavic and East European languages collection (SML), Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Slavic and East European languages collection (SML), G, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Slavic and East European languages collection (SML), S, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Social Science library, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Social Science library, G, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Social Science library, S, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Southeast Asia collection (SML), Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Southeast Asia collection (SML), G, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Southeast Asia collection (SML), S, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Statistics library, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Statistics library, S, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Sterling Memorial Library (SML), Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Systems' office (SML), Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Systems' office (SML), G, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Wing STC (SML), G and S, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Yale Center for British Art, including Rare Book collection and Reference collection, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Yale Center for British Art, G; including Rare Book collection, and Reference collection, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Yale Center for British Art, S; including Rare Book collection and Reference collection, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Annual report, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Annual reports, non Yale, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Annual report, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Statistics, annual report, forms, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Statistics, annual report, miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - MSS processing instructions, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Planning documents, TS, 1979-1993 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Statistics, annual report, master copy (parts 1 and 2), 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 42-43)
- Records, 1981-1987; Accession 1998-A-051
  - Family papers, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allan Pond papers, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Worrell, Albert C., papers, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Schmidt, Henry; papers, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Acquisitions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Accessions, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Accessions, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Accessions, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Africana collection, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arbitration, December 2, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Archives, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Asakawa papers, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - BRBL, miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - BAC, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CAIE, functions, vocabulary, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Commonwealth fund, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - DEST, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Divinity library, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Drama, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Espy, miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Evaluations, January 30, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Famulus Galley Program, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Job descriptions, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - MCL, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - LAPC register, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Mahler, Margaret S., papers, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Management bibliography, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Manuscripts and Archives memos, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - MAPS resources, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Library of Congress microfilm to be catalogued, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Yale lectures, Tully, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Microfilm notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Microfilm records without finding aids, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Microfilm, authority catalog, Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Microfilm information sheets, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Parliamentary History film, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Microfilm camera, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Microfilm publications, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Microfilm, preservation, costs, instructions, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - New England Archivists, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - New England Achivists, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - New England Archivists, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - The National Union Catalog of Manuscripts Collections, 1952-1965 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - The National Union Catalog of Manuscripts Collections, Cornell, Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Objects exhibit, Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Optical scanner, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Poster collection, Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Poster workform, subject lists, Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Poster workform, original and explanation, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Exhibit PR exhibit, Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Famulus printouts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Yale Art Gallery (Y.A.G.) poster inventory, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Posters, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Posters, U.S.F., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Ezra Pound search, Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Preservation survey records, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Preservation report, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Preservation projects, Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Processing lists, Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Processing memos, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Library research programs, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - RLIN terminal accounts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - RLIN project meeting, April 1985 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - RLIN, error report form, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - RLIN, reference, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - PRS reports, July 29, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Archives, personal papers, and manuscripts, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - RLIN, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Abstracts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - RLIN memos, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Research Libraries Group, inc.1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - RRS reports, "Acts", 1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Weber, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - RLIN, users, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - RLIN, misc., January 1, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - RLIN, mail, January 1, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - RLIN/AMC, stats (weekly), 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - RLIN/AMC stats (weekly), 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - RLIN, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Overview of implementation of RLIN authorities system, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Reference department, January 20, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Shredder machine manual, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Silliman, B., annual reports, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Silliman photo, to be catalogued for Silliman family papers, 1818 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - S.A.A., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - S.A.A., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - S.A.A. newsletter, ballot, and bulletin, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - S.A.A. mail, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Staff schedules, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Yale University library, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Student applications, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Technical services, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Technical services, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Manuscripts and archives, technical services, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Unit memos, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Processing surveys and lists, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Jewish Genealogy: An Annotated Bibliography, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Note on original container, September 25, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Title II-C project, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Title II-C, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Title II-C grant, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Weather policy, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Xerox statistics, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Yale staff news, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Modern Archives and Manuscripts: A Select Bibliography, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Manuscript group number list, funding aid code, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Finding evaluations, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Yale record groups, Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - American Museum of Natural History, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - The History of Medicine collection, Undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Manuscripts and Archives lists, Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - HML, History of Medical library, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Medical History library (parts 1 and 2), 1960-1982 (Box 2, Folder 54-55)
  - Historical Medical collections, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Physician's daybooks, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (parts 1 and 2), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - RLIN, mail, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Functional requirements for manuscripts and archives system II, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Functional requirements for manuscripts and archives III, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Request for proposals for an integrated library system for Cornell University libraries, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Archival research and evaluation staff, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - RLIN meeting, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - RLIN, Tucker's overview paper, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Film orders, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Video archives, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Data elements in the process control transaction file, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - RLIN notebook, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm orders, incoming, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous projects, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Richard Lee, taping from February 26, 1978, February 28, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Divinity library, 1970-1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Students, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - MCL, Lynn S., 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Sinderen, Van, collection, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Beinecke Rare Book Library (BRBL), exhibit, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Staff development, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Provenance, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Information for Bill to use with guides, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Film, problems, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - A Descriptive Guide to the University Archives of Temple University, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - The Garfield Orbit, The Life of President James A. Garfield, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Some suggestions for the protection of books and manuscripts in a home library, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - The Society of American Archivists, 49th annual meeting, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Unit description, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Staff performance evaluation, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Harrison, John; James A. Donovan papers, March 21, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Shaw collection, Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Finding aid list, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - An appraisal process for the records of Science and Technology, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Society of American Archivists session, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Society of American Archivists, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Grant NU, statements, reports of expenditures, bookkeeping, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Yale geographical data and other data, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Society of American Archivists paper, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Wright, Howell, August 8, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - American Museum of Natural History, subject term printout, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Family History, new opportunities for archivists, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Microfilming, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Wesleyan University, 1974-1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Open collections, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Records of Don Waters, 1987-1993; Accession 2000-A-013
  - Advisory Committee on Information Technology (3) (Box 1)
    - Fall 1995 (Box 1)
    - 1996-1997 (2) (Box 1)
  - Bibliographic Utilities (Box 1)
    - Group (Box 1)
    - Proposal (Box 1)
  - British Library (Box 1)
  - Budget C) (Box 1)
    - FY 89/90 - RLIN (Box 1)
    - FY 91/92 (Box 1)
      - Gifts (Box 1)
      - Orbis (Box 1)
      - Photocopy (Box 1)
      - Position Control (Box 1)
      - Quarterly Reports (Box 1)
      - RLIN (2) (Box 1)
      - Travel (Box 1)
    - FY 92/93 (Box 1)
      - Beinecke (Box 1)
      - Budget Book Text (Box 1)
      - Cash Balances (Box 1)
      - Fees and Fines (Box 1)
      - General (Box 1)
      - Gifts (Box 1)
      - Guidelines (Box 1)
      - Orbis (Box 1)
      - Photocopy (Box 1)
      - Position Control (Box 1)
      - Proposal (Box 1)
      - Quarterly Reports (Box 1)
      - RLIN Costs (Box 1)
      - Summary (Box 1)
    - FY 93/94 (Box 1)
      - Assessments (Box 1)
      - Block III (Box 1)
      - Equipment (Box 1)
      - Fees and Fines (Box 1)
      - Fund Balances (Box 1)
      - Gifts (Box 1)
      - Income (Box 1)
      - fvIedical Library (Box 1)
      - fv1icrofilm Unit (Box 1)
      - Monitoring Reports (Box 1)
      - Nota Bene (Box 1)
      - Part-time wages (Box 1)
      - Photocopy (Box 1)
      - Position control (Box 1)
      - Proposal (Box 1)
      - Quarterly Reports (Box 1)
      - Renovation Fund (Box 1)
      - Staffmg Reallocation (Box 1)
      - Travel (Box 1)
      - UBC Presentation (Box 1)
      - Year End Savings (Box 1)
    - FY 94/95
      - Assessments (Box 2)
      - Block III (Box 2)
      - Books (Box 2)
      - Budget Book Text (Box 2)
      - CCL (Box 2)
      - Equipment (Box 2)
      - Fines (Box 2)
      - Fund Balances (Box 2)
      - Gifts (Box 2)
      - Guidelines Proposal (Box 2)
      - Income (Box 2)
      - lvfedical Library (Box 2)
      - O'Neill Fund (Box 2)
      - Part time Wages (Box 2)
      - Proposal (Box 2)
      - Provost BriefIng (Box 2)
      - Quarterly Reports (Box 2)
      - Special Collection Endowment (Box 2)
      - Special Fund Balances (Box 2)
      - Summary Expenses (Box 2)
      - Travel (Box 2)
    - FY 95/96 (Box 2)
      - Assessments (Box 2)
      - Budget Reduction (Box 2)
      - Collection Budget (Box 2)
      - End of Year Processing (Box 2)
      - Endowment Income (Box 2)
      - Fees and Fines (Box 2)
      - Gifts (Box 2)
      - Mellon Endowment (Box 2)
      - Orbis Charges (Box 2)
      - Part-time Wages (Box 2)
      - Potential Funding Problems (Box 2)
      - Position Funding Review (Box 2)
      - Proposal (Box 2)
      - Salary, Wages and BenefIts (Box 2)
      - Status Reports (Box 2)
      - Strike Savings (Box 2)
      - Travel (Box 2)
      - Travel Reports (Box 2)
      - Turnover Savings (Box 2)
      - Vacancy Savings (Box 2)
  - Commission on Preservation and Access (CPA) (Box 2)
    - Digital Preservation (Box 2)
    - Planning Grant (Box 2)
      - Open Book Phase I (Box 2)
  - Committee on Online Scholarly Information (COSI) (2) (Box 2)
    - Agenda (Box 2)
    - GRL Files (Box 2)
    - Minutes (Box 2)
    - Navigation Committee (Box 2)
    - Retreat, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Computing and Information Systems (CandIS) (Box 2)
    - Budget (Box 2)
    - Computing Committee (Box 2)
    - Daemons (Box 2)
    - Facilities Management (Box 2)
      - Review, 1989 March (Box 2)
      - Review, 1992 April (Box 2)
    - Ferguson Review (Box 2)
    - Monthly Statements (Box 2)
    - Pricing (Box 2)
    - Pricing, 1995 (Box 2)
    - YUL Planning (Box 2)
      - Unix Proposal (Box 2)
    - Volume Recovery (Box 2)
  - Core Project (Box 2)
  - Cornell University (Box 2)
    - Digital Preservation (Box 2)
    - Mandarin Project (Box 2)
    - Mann Library (Box 2)
    - Virtual Library (Box 2)
    - Visit (Box 2)
  - CCL (Box 3)
    - Courtyard Leaks (Box 3)
    - Security System (Box 3)
  - Digital Library (Box 3)
    - At Yale (Box 3)
    - Digital Preservation Consortium (Box 3)
      - Mission and Goals (Box 3)
      - Project Managers (Box 3)
    - Electronic Classroom (Box 3)
    - Electronic Course Reserves (Box 3)
    - Humanities Texts (Box 3)
  - Digital Preservation Symposium (Box 3)
  - Divinity Library (Box 3)
    - Benchmarking (Box 3)
    - Budget (Box 3)
    - Luce Proposal (Box 3)
  - East Asian Collection - Union List ofJapanese Serials (Box 3)
  - East Asian Studies (Box 3)
  - EBSCO (Box 3)
  - Economic Growth Center (Box 3)
  - Electronic Text Center (Box 3)
  - Equipment Requests (Box 3)
    - FY 89/90 (Box 3)
    - FY 91/92 (Box 3)
    - FY 92/93 (Box 3)
    - FY 93/94 (Box 3)
    - FY 94/95 (Box 3)
      - Non-Automation (Box 3)
    - FY 95/96 (Box 3)
      - Midyear (Box 3)
    - FY 96/97 (Box 3)
      - Midyear (Box 3)
    - Procedures (Box 3)
  - Future of Systems (Box 3)
    - National Library of Canada, 1994 August (Box 3)
  - Harvard Depository Library (Box 3)
  - Harvard - Emory - Yale (HEY) (Box 3)
    - African American Art Project (Box 3)
    - Education Institute (Box 3)
    - Initiative (Box 3)
    - Newspaper Project (Box 3)
    - Project (Box 3)
  - Harvard Library (Box 3)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Rights and Responsibilities (Box 3)
    - Gateway (Box 3)
  - Hewlett Foundation (Box 3)
  - Historical Sound Recordings (Box 3)
  - Human Relations Area Files (Box 3)
  - Information Technologies Architecture Task Force (ITATF) (Box 3)
    - Documents (Box 3)
    - Reports (Box 3)
  - Information Technology - Fuchs Report (Box 3)
  - InformationTechnology Service (ITS) - Budget, Fall 1996 (Box 4)
  - Innovatlve Interfaces (Box 4)
    - CJK (Box 4)
  - Instant Math Preprints (Box 4)
  - International Systems Services (ISS) (Box 4)
  - Kanazawa Institute ofTechnology Library Center (Box 4)
  - LaGuardia Eight (Box 4)
    - Presentation, 1991 July (Box 4)
  - Latin American Manuscripts Access Grant (Box 4)
  - Latin American Research Resources Project (Box 4)
  - Monograph Acquistions (Box 4)
  - Library of Congress (Box 4)
    - Cataloging Efficiency (Box 4)
    - Conference on Organizing Digital :tvIaterials (Box 4)
    - Consulting (Box 4)
      - Fall 1995 (Box 4)
      - Mar 1995 (Box 4)
      - Aug 1995 (Box 4)
    - Digital Library (Box 4)
    - Project Open Book Presentation, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Library Planning and Budget Committee (LPBC) 1,2 and 3 (3) (Box 4)
    - Agenda (Box 5)
    - Budget Subcommittee (Box 5)
    - Committee Structure (Box 5)
    - Minutes (Box 5)
    - Process (Box 5)
    - Special Projects FY 92/93 (Box 5)
    - Special Projects FY 93/94 (Box 5)
  - Mainframe Database (Box 5)
    - Committee (Box 5)
    - Folio (Box 5)
    - Pricing (Box 5)
    - Retreat (Box 5)
    - Yellow Pages (Box 5)
  - Management Information (Box 5)
    - Acquisitions (Box 5)
  - Management Team - Retreat, 1996 January (Box 5)
  - MandP Salary Committee (Box 5)
    - Classification and Salary Review (Box 5)
    - Salary Increases, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Salary Structure (Box 5)
  - Manuscripts and Archives (Box 5)
    - Accession Management (Box 5)
    - Finding Aids (Box 5)
    - Security (Box 5)
    - Space (Box 5)
  - Maps (Box 5)
  - Mellon Foundation (Box 5)
    - Library Technology Program (Box 5)
    - Music (Box 5)
  - Mellon Grant (Box 5)
  - Mellon Project (Box 5)
  - Microcomputer (Box 5)
    - Advisory Board (2) (Box 5)
    - Maintenance (Box 5)
    - Support (Box 5)
      - Communique (Box 5)
      - Equipment Selection Guidelines (Box 5)
      - Expert Users (Box 5)
      - Orbis Download (Box 5)
      - PC Classes (Box 5)
      - Spare Parts (Box 5)
      - Staff (Box 5)
      - Statistics (Box 5)
      - Task Force on Acquiring Software (Box 5)
      - Where Are We?, 1988 February (Box 5)
  - Microfilm to Digital Imagery (Box 5)
    - Final Draft (Box 5)
  - Music Library (Box 5)
  - MPG (Box 5)
  - Near East Curator (Box 5)
  - NETMENU (Box 5)
  - Network Fiber Plan (Box 5)
  - Network Navigation (Box 5)
  - Network Vision (Box 5)
    - Spring 94 (Box 5)
  - Networked Information - Gopher (Box 5)
  - Networks and Networking at Yale (Box 5)
  - Networks - Hillhouse Avenue (Box 5)
  - New Haven Public Health Database (Box 5)
  - New Haven Vital Statistics (Box 5)
  - Newspaper Digitizing (Box 5)
  - NEXIS (Box 5)
  - Northeast Research Libraries (Box 5)
  - NOTIS (Box 6)
    - 5.1 Implementation (Box 6)
    - Ameritech (Box 6)
    - Basic Support Policy (Box 6)
    - Bills and Payments (Box 6)
    - Contract (Box 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 6)
    - Customer Profile (Box 6)
    - Customer Service Reviews (Box 6)
    - Installations at Yale (Box 6)
    - LBC30 (Box 6)
    - Library Review (Box 6)
    - LMS IYlaintenance Fees (Box 6)
    - Maintenance Rates (Box 6)
    - QuikMerge (Box 6)
    - RLIN Users (Box 6)
    - TechLINK (Box 6)
    - User Group Meetings (Box 6)
      - 1988 (Box 6)
      - 1989 (Box 6)
      - 1990 (Box 6)
      - 1991 (Box 6)
      - 1992 (Box 6)
      - 1994 (Box 6)
  - OCLC (Box 6)
    - RLAC (Box 6)
      - Conference (Box 6)
      - Talk (Box 6)
    - Statements (Box 6)
  - ORBIS (Box 6)
    - AITF to OCG (Box 6)
    - Approval Plans (Box 6)
    - Availability (Box 6)
    - Availability Reports (Box 6)
    - Budget (Box 6)
      - Data Communications Costs (Box 6)
      - Funding (Box 6)
      - Preliminary Analysis of Costs (Box 6)